<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>tips - Tag - DSucceed</title>
        <link>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/tags/tips/</link>
        <description>tips - Tag - DSucceed</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>dsucceeded@gmail.com (Sandeep Undrakonda)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>dsucceeded@gmail.com (Sandeep Undrakonda)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 11:30:31 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/tags/tips/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Mastering the Secrets of OOP: Inheritance, Polymorphism, Abstraction, and Encapsulation</title>
    <link>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/posts/oops_101/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 11:30:31 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Sandeep Undrakonda</author>
    <guid>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/posts/oops_101/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/blog/oops101.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>oops 101Inheritance, Polymorphism, Abstraction, and Encapsulation: Pillars of Object-Oriented Programming Welcome to this fun and informative blog post where we&rsquo;ll dive into some important concepts of object-oriented programming: inheritance, polymorphism, abstraction, and encapsulation. These concepts form the foundation of modern software development and play a crucial role in creating reusable, modular, and maintainable code. So, let&rsquo;s get started and explore each concept in detail, with a touch of fun along the way!]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Cracking the Code: Your Ultimate Guide to Software Job Success!</title>
    <link>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/posts/starter-pack/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:21:39 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Sandeep Undrakonda</author>
    <guid>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/posts/starter-pack/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/blog/gettoit.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Get To ItAre You a Student Desperately Wanting a Software Job? Make Sure You Tick These Boxes to Ace Your Software Job Interviews! Hey there, fellow students! So, you know you need a job, but you&rsquo;re not quite sure where to start, right? Don&rsquo;t worry, we&rsquo;ve got your back. We understand the struggle of being an ambitious student in India, feeling betrayed by your college&rsquo;s lack of placements and facing unfair competition.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
