<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>DSucceed</title>
        <link>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/</link>
        <description>Your One Stop For D Succees</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>dsucceeded@gmail.com (Sandeep Undrakonda)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>dsucceeded@gmail.com (Sandeep Undrakonda)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 07:18:32 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Mastering the Art of Coding with LeetCode: The Quest for the Coveted T-Shirt</title>
    <link>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/posts/leetcode-tshirt/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 07:18:32 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Sandeep Undrakonda</author>
    <guid>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/posts/leetcode-tshirt/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/blog/tshirt.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>T-ShirtThe LeetCode T-Shirt: A Journey of Patience, Dedication, and Perseverance Introduction: In the world of coding, there is a special T-shirt that is coveted by programmers everywhere. It&rsquo;s not a designer brand, nor is it particularly stylish. But it is a symbol of something greater. This T-shirt is from LeetCode, a popular platform for coding challenges, and it is not something you can just swipe your card and buy at the store.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Beware the Unleashed Writer: The Fearful Power of ChatGPT&#39;s Automated Articles</title>
    <link>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/posts/beware-the-unleashed-writer-the-fearful-power-of-chatgpts-automated-articles/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 15:58:26 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Sandeep Undrakonda</author>
    <guid>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/posts/beware-the-unleashed-writer-the-fearful-power-of-chatgpts-automated-articles/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/blog/chatgpt.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>The Rise of Automated Article Writing with ChatGPT Have you ever wondered if a machine or a human wrote an article you&rsquo;re reading? With ChatGPT, the answer is both. This technology has revolutionized the world of writing and made it accessible to everyone.
The Power of Language Models ChatGPT, based on GPT-3.5 architecture, is a large language model that uses machine learning to generate human-like text. Trained on a massive amount of data, including books, articles, and websites, ChatGPT is capable of producing a wide range of texts, from emails to novels.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
