<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Job Updates - Category - DSucceed</title>
        <link>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/categories/job-updates/</link>
        <description>Job Updates - Category - DSucceed</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>dsucceeded@gmail.com (Sandeep Undrakonda)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>dsucceeded@gmail.com (Sandeep Undrakonda)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 16:36:50 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/categories/job-updates/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Siemens is Hiring For Software Engineer Associatee</title>
    <link>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/posts/siemens-is-hiring/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 16:36:50 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Sandeep Undrakonda</author>
    <guid>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/posts/siemens-is-hiring/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/blog/siemens.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>SeimensCompany: Seimens (Link At Bottom) Job Title:Software Engineer Intern Job Description: The Software Engineer Intern will assist more senior engineers in designing, developing, modifying, and implementing software programming for products (both internal and external). The intern will work under close supervision and will be responsible for ensuring the overall functional quality of the released product on all required platforms and mechanisms.
Responsibilities: Assist more senior engineers in designing, developing, modifying, and implementing software programming for products (both internal and external).]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Pragma Edge is Hiring For QA Engineer Associate</title>
    <link>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/posts/pragmaedge-is-hiring/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:10:22 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Sandeep Undrakonda</author>
    <guid>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/posts/pragmaedge-is-hiring/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/blog/pragmaEdge.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>PragmaEdgeCompany: PragmaEdge (Link At Bottom) Job Title: Software Quality Assurance Engineer Job Description: The Software Quality Assurance Engineer plays a critical role in ensuring the quality and reliability of software products through effective testing and validation. They review requirements, design documents, and specifications to provide valuable feedback and create comprehensive test plans and cases. Additionally, they develop and execute automation scripts, track and document bugs, and perform regression testing.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Varian is Hiring For Software Engineer</title>
    <link>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/posts/varian-software-engineer/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 16:29:28 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Sandeep Undrakonda</author>
    <guid>https://dsucceed.github.io/blog/posts/varian-software-engineer/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/blog/varian.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>VarianCompany: Varian (Link At Bottom) Job Title: Software Developer - Oncology Solutions Job Description: As a Software Developer at Varian, a Siemens Healthineers Company, your role is vital in fighting cancer. We develop user-friendly and efficient software solutions for oncology. Our goal is to create a world without fear of cancer. You will work closely with a team of developers and testers to contribute to this mission. Strong programming skills in Java are a must, and experience with an additional language like Golang, Python, Kotlin, or JavaScript is a plus.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
